var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "523",
        "rootWordId": 12,
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": 549,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ فَيَقُولُ هَاؤُمُ اقْرَءُوا كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ت ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "آتَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to give",
        "waznTlit": "ātā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "524",
        "rootWordId": 12,
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": 549,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِشِمَالِهِ فَيَقُولُ يَا لَيْتَنِي لَمْ أُوتَ كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ت ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "آتَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to give",
        "waznTlit": "ātā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتَ",
        "answer": "I had been given",
        "pcklId": "525",
        "rootWordId": 12,
        "tlit": "ūta",
        "frequency": 549,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 9,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِشِمَالِهِ فَيَقُولُ يَا لَيْتَنِي لَمْ أُوتَ كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ت ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "آتَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to give",
        "waznTlit": "ātā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "rootWordId": 20,
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": 85,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 47,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَا مِنْكُمْ مِنْ أَحَدٍ عَنْهُ حَاجِزِينَ",
        "rootWord": "أ ح د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَحَد",
        "waznEnglish": "one, anyone",
        "waznTlit": "aḥad",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 74,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَهُمْ",
        "answer": "so He seized them",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "rootWordId": 21,
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhahum",
        "frequency": 273,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَعَصَوْا رَسُولَ رَبِّهِمْ فَأَخَذَهُمْ أَخْذَةً رَابِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "أ خ ذ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَخَذَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to take, to seize",
        "waznTlit": "akhadha",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 127,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذُوهُ",
        "answer": "Seize him",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "rootWordId": 21,
        "tlit": "khudhūhu",
        "frequency": 273,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 30,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " خُذُوهُ فَغُلُّوهُ",
        "rootWord": "أ خ ذ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَخَذَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to take, to seize",
        "waznTlit": "akhadha",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 127,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "Certainly We (would) have seized",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "rootWordId": 21,
        "tlit": "la-akhadhnā",
        "frequency": 273,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 45,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " لَأَخَذْنَا مِنْهُ بِالْيَمِينِ",
        "rootWord": "أ خ ذ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَخَذَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to take, to seize",
        "waznTlit": "akhadha",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 127,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْذَةً",
        "answer": "(with) a seizure",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "rootWordId": 21,
        "tlit": "akhdhatan",
        "frequency": 273,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَعَصَوْا رَسُولَ رَبِّهِمْ فَأَخَذَهُمْ أَخْذَةً رَابِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "أ خ ذ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَخْذ",
        "waznEnglish": "taking, seizure",
        "waznTlit": "akhdh",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then when",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": 409,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَإِذَا نُفِخَ فِي الصُّورِ نَفْخَةٌ وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 409,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أُذُنٌ",
        "answer": "an ear",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "rootWordId": 29,
        "tlit": "udhunun",
        "frequency": 102,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " لِنَجْعَلَهَا لَكُمْ تَذْكِرَةً وَتَعِيَهَا أُذُنٌ وَاعِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "أ ذ ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أُذُنٌ",
        "waznEnglish": "ear",
        "waznTlit": "udhunun",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 18,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "rootWordId": 32,
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": 461,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَحُمِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ وَالْجِبَالُ فَدُكَّتَا دَكَّةً وَاحِدَةً",
        "rootWord": "أ ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ر ض",
        "waznEnglish": "the Earth, land",
        "waznTlit": "hamza rā ḍād",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 461,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُؤْتَفِكَاتُ",
        "answer": "and the overturned cities",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "rootWordId": 52,
        "tlit": "wal-mu'tafikātu",
        "frequency": 30,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَجَاءَ فِرْعَوْنُ وَمَنْ قَبْلَهُ وَالْمُؤْتَفِكَاتُ بِالْخَاطِئَةِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ف ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُؤْتَفِكَة",
        "waznEnglish": "overturned cities",
        "waznTlit": "mu'tafikat",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form VIII)",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "rootWordId": 54,
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": 109,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " كُلُوا وَاشْرَبُوا هَنِيئًا بِمَا أَسْلَفْتُمْ فِي الْأَيَّامِ الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ك ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَكَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to eat, to consume",
        "waznTlit": "akala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 93,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُهُ",
        "answer": "will eat it",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "rootWordId": 54,
        "tlit": "yakuluhu",
        "frequency": 109,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 37,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا يَأْكُلُهُ إِلَّا الْخَاطِئُونَ",
        "rootWord": "أ ك ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَكَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to eat, to consume",
        "waznTlit": "akala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 93,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "536",
        "rootWordId": 58,
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": 663,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 36,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا طَعَامٌ إِلَّا مِنْ غِسْلِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "إِلَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "except",
        "waznTlit": "illā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Restriction particle)",
        "waznFreq": 663,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "537",
        "rootWordId": 58,
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": 663,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 37,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا يَأْكُلُهُ إِلَّا الْخَاطِئُونَ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "إِلَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "except",
        "waznTlit": "illā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Restriction particle)",
        "waznFreq": 663,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2791",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": 2851,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 33,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ كَانَ لَا يُؤْمِنُ بِاللَّهِ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun",
        "waznFreq": 2699,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "So as for",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "rootWordId": 73,
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": 55,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا ثَمُودُ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِالطَّاغِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "أَمَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "أَمَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "Then as for",
        "waznTlit": "ammā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Explanation particle)",
        "waznFreq": 55,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "And as for",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "rootWordId": 73,
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": 55,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا عَادٌ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِرِيحٍ صَرْصَرٍ عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "أَمَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "أَمَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "Then as for",
        "waznTlit": "ammā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Explanation particle)",
        "waznFreq": 55,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then as for",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "rootWordId": 73,
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": 55,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ فَيَقُولُ هَاؤُمُ اقْرَءُوا كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "أَمَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "أَمَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "Then as for",
        "waznTlit": "ammā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Explanation particle)",
        "waznFreq": 55,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "rootWordId": 73,
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": 55,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِشِمَالِهِ فَيَقُولُ يَا لَيْتَنِي لَمْ أُوتَ كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "أَمَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "أَمَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "Then as for",
        "waznTlit": "ammā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Explanation particle)",
        "waznFreq": 55,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believing",
        "pcklId": "539",
        "rootWordId": 75,
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": 879,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 33,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ كَانَ لَا يُؤْمِنُ بِاللَّهِ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "أ م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ءَامَنَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to believe",
        "waznTlit": "āmana",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 537,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "you believe",
        "pcklId": "540",
        "rootWordId": 75,
        "tlit": "tu'minūna",
        "frequency": 879,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 41,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِقَوْلِ شَاعِرٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "rootWord": "أ م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ءَامَنَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to believe",
        "waznTlit": "āmana",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 537,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "rootWordId": 129,
        "tlit": "tub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": 148,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 38,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَا أُقْسِمُ بِمَا تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ب ص ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَبْصَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "abṣara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 29,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "rootWordId": 129,
        "tlit": "tub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": 148,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 39,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا لَا تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ب ص ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَبْصَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "abṣara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 29,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضَ",
        "answer": "some",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "rootWordId": 141,
        "tlit": "baʿḍa",
        "frequency": 158,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 44,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَوْ تَقَوَّلَ عَلَيْنَا بَعْضَ الْأَقَاوِيلِ",
        "rootWord": "ب ع ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَعْض",
        "waznEnglish": "some of you",
        "waznTlit": "baʿḍ",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 157,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاقِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "remains",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "rootWordId": 150,
        "tlit": "bāqiyatin",
        "frequency": 21,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَهَلْ تَرَىٰ لَهُمْ مِنْ بَاقِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ب ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَاقِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "remained",
        "waznTlit": "bāqiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "eight",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "rootWordId": 209,
        "tlit": "thamāniyatun",
        "frequency": 19,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 9,
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَحْمِلُ عَرْشَ رَبِّكَ فَوْقَهُمْ يَوْمَئِذٍ ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ث م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ثَمَٰنِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and the eight of them",
        "waznTlit": "thamāniyat",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَثَمَانِيَةَ",
        "answer": "and eight",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "rootWordId": 209,
        "tlit": "wathamāniyata",
        "frequency": 19,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " سَخَّرَهَا عَلَيْهِمْ سَبْعَ لَيَالٍ وَثَمَانِيَةَ أَيَّامٍ حُسُومًا",
        "rootWord": "ث م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ثَمَٰنِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and the eight of them",
        "waznTlit": "thamāniyat",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِبَالُ",
        "answer": "and the mountains",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "rootWordId": 219,
        "tlit": "wal-jibālu",
        "frequency": 41,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَحُمِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ وَالْجِبَالُ فَدُكَّتَا دَكَّةً وَاحِدَةً",
        "rootWord": "ج ب ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَبَل",
        "waznEnglish": "hill",
        "waznTlit": "jabal",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 39,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَحِيمَ",
        "answer": "(into) the Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "rootWordId": 227,
        "tlit": "l-jaḥīma",
        "frequency": 26,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 31,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ الْجَحِيمَ صَلُّوهُ",
        "rootWord": "ج ح م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ج ح م",
        "waznEnglish": "(of) the blazing Fire",
        "waznTlit": "jīm ḥā mīm",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 26,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَارِيَةِ",
        "answer": "the sailing (ship)",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "rootWordId": 242,
        "tlit": "l-jāriyati",
        "frequency": 64,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّا لَمَّا طَغَى الْمَاءُ حَمَلْنَاكُمْ فِي الْجَارِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ج ر ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَارِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "flow",
        "waznTlit": "jāriyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَجْعَلَهَا",
        "answer": "That We might make it",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "rootWordId": 249,
        "tlit": "linajʿalahā",
        "frequency": 346,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " لِنَجْعَلَهَا لَكُمْ تَذْكِرَةً وَتَعِيَهَا أُذُنٌ وَاعِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ج ع ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَعَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to make",
        "waznTlit": "jaʿala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 340,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّةٍ",
        "answer": "a Garden",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "rootWordId": 267,
        "tlit": "jannatin",
        "frequency": 201,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 22,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فِي جَنَّةٍ عَالِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ج ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جَنَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "covered",
        "waznTlit": "jannat",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 147,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءَ",
        "answer": "And came",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "rootWordId": 281,
        "tlit": "wajāa",
        "frequency": 278,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَجَاءَ فِرْعَوْنُ وَمَنْ قَبْلَهُ وَالْمُؤْتَفِكَاتُ بِالْخَاطِئَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ج ي أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ج ي أ",
        "waznEnglish": "to come",
        "waznTlit": "jīm yā hamza",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 278,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاجِزِينَ",
        "answer": "(who could) prevent (it)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 295,
        "tlit": "ḥājizīna",
        "frequency": 2,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 47,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَا مِنْكُمْ مِنْ أَحَدٍ عَنْهُ حَاجِزِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ح ج ز",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَٰجِزِين",
        "waznEnglish": "a barrier",
        "waznTlit": "ḥājizīn",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my account",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "rootWordId": 316,
        "tlit": "ḥisābiyah",
        "frequency": 109,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 20,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنِّي ظَنَنْتُ أَنِّي مُلَاقٍ حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ح س ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حِسَاب",
        "waznEnglish": "(do) you think",
        "waznTlit": "ḥisāb",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form III) (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 39,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "(is) my account",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "rootWordId": 316,
        "tlit": "ḥisābiyah",
        "frequency": 109,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 26,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَمْ أَدْرِ مَا حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ح س ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حِسَاب",
        "waznEnglish": "(do) you think",
        "waznTlit": "ḥisāb",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form III) (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 39,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَحَسْرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a regret",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "rootWordId": 318,
        "tlit": "laḥasratun",
        "frequency": 12,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 50,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّهُ لَحَسْرَةٌ عَلَى الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ح س ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَسْرَة",
        "waznEnglish": "they tire",
        "waznTlit": "ḥasrat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 7,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حُسُومًا",
        "answer": "(in) succession",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 320,
        "tlit": "ḥusūman",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " سَخَّرَهَا عَلَيْهِمْ سَبْعَ لَيَالٍ وَثَمَانِيَةَ أَيَّامٍ حُسُومًا",
        "rootWord": "ح س م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ح س م",
        "waznEnglish": "(in) succession",
        "waznTlit": "ḥā sīn mīm",
        "waznType": "Adjective",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحُضُّ",
        "answer": "feel the urge",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 331,
        "tlit": "yaḥuḍḍu",
        "frequency": 3,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 34,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَحُضُّ عَلَىٰ طَعَامِ الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ح ض ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَحُضُّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to feel the urge",
        "waznTlit": "yaḥuḍḍu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَحَقُّ",
        "answer": "surely (the) truth",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "rootWordId": 344,
        "tlit": "laḥaqqu",
        "frequency": 287,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 51,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّهُ لَحَقُّ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ح ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَقّ",
        "waznEnglish": "deserved ",
        "waznTlit": "ḥaqq",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 247,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "answer": "The Inevitable Reality",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "rootWordId": 344,
        "tlit": "al-ḥāqatu",
        "frequency": 287,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "rootWord": "ح ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَآقَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "deserved ",
        "waznTlit": "ḥāqqat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Inevitable Reality",
        "pcklId": "285",
        "rootWordId": 344,
        "tlit": "l-ḥāqatu",
        "frequency": 287,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " مَا الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "rootWord": "ح ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَآقَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "deserved ",
        "waznTlit": "ḥāqqat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Inevitable Reality",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "rootWordId": 344,
        "tlit": "l-ḥāqatu",
        "frequency": 287,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا أَدْرَاكَ مَا الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "rootWord": "ح ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَآقَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "deserved ",
        "waznTlit": "ḥāqqat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We carried you",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "rootWordId": 354,
        "tlit": "ḥamalnākum",
        "frequency": 64,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّا لَمَّا طَغَى الْمَاءُ حَمَلْنَاكُمْ فِي الْجَارِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ح م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَمَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to carry, to bear",
        "waznTlit": "ḥamala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 41,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُمِلَتِ",
        "answer": "And are lifted",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "rootWordId": 354,
        "tlit": "waḥumilati",
        "frequency": 64,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَحُمِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ وَالْجِبَالُ فَدُكَّتَا دَكَّةً وَاحِدَةً",
        "rootWord": "ح م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَمَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to carry, to bear",
        "waznTlit": "ḥamala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 41,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَحْمِلُ",
        "answer": "and will bear",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "rootWordId": 354,
        "tlit": "wayaḥmilu",
        "frequency": 64,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَحْمِلُ عَرْشَ رَبِّكَ فَوْقَهُمْ يَوْمَئِذٍ ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ح م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَمَلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to carry, to bear",
        "waznTlit": "ḥamala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 41,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيمٌ",
        "answer": "any devoted friend",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 355,
        "tlit": "ḥamīmun",
        "frequency": 21,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 35,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَيْسَ لَهُ الْيَوْمَ هَاهُنَا حَمِيمٌ",
        "rootWord": "ح م م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَمِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "boiling water",
        "waznTlit": "ḥamīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 20,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْخَاطِئَةِ",
        "answer": "with sin",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "rootWordId": 417,
        "tlit": "bil-khāṭi-ati",
        "frequency": 22,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " وَجَاءَ فِرْعَوْنُ وَمَنْ قَبْلَهُ وَالْمُؤْتَفِكَاتُ بِالْخَاطِئَةِ",
        "rootWord": "خ ط أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَاطِئَة",
        "waznEnglish": "we err",
        "waznTlit": "khāṭi-at",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاطِئُونَ",
        "answer": "the sinners",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "rootWordId": 417,
        "tlit": "l-khāṭiūna",
        "frequency": 22,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 37,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " لَا يَأْكُلُهُ إِلَّا الْخَاطِئُونَ",
        "rootWord": "خ ط أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَٰطِـِٔين",
        "waznEnglish": "we err",
        "waznTlit": "khāṭiīn",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْفَىٰ",
        "answer": "will be hidden",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 425,
        "tlit": "takhfā",
        "frequency": 34,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 18,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ تُعْرَضُونَ لَا تَخْفَىٰ مِنْكُمْ خَافِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "خ ف ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَخْفَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to hide",
        "waznTlit": "yakhfā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خَافِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "any secret",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "rootWordId": 425,
        "tlit": "khāfiyatun",
        "frequency": 34,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 18,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ تُعْرَضُونَ لَا تَخْفَىٰ مِنْكُمْ خَافِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "خ ف ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَافِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "is hidden",
        "waznTlit": "khāfiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "answer": "past",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "rootWordId": 433,
        "tlit": "l-khāliyati",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 8,
        "arabicAyah": " كُلُوا وَاشْرَبُوا هَنِيئًا بِمَا أَسْلَفْتُمْ فِي الْأَيَّامِ الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "خ ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَالِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "they are alone",
        "waznTlit": "khāliyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "hollow",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 447,
        "tlit": "khāwiyatin",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 15,
        "arabicAyah": " فَتَرَى الْقَوْمَ فِيهَا صَرْعَىٰ كَأَنَّهُمْ أَعْجَازُ نَخْلٍ خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "خ و ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خ و ي",
        "waznEnglish": "(had) overturned",
        "waznTlit": "khā wāw yā",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرِ",
        "answer": "I had known",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "rootWordId": 469,
        "tlit": "adri",
        "frequency": 29,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 26,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَمْ أَدْرِ مَا حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "د ر ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَدْرِى",
        "waznEnglish": "to know",
        "waznTlit": "tadrī",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرَاكَ",
        "answer": "will make you know",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "rootWordId": 469,
        "tlit": "adrāka",
        "frequency": 29,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا أَدْرَاكَ مَا الْحَاقَّةُ",
        "rootWord": "د ر ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَدْرَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to make known",
        "waznTlit": "adrā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 17,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَدُكَّتَا",
        "answer": "and crushed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 478,
        "tlit": "fadukkatā",
        "frequency": 7,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَحُمِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ وَالْجِبَالُ فَدُكَّتَا دَكَّةً وَاحِدَةً",
        "rootWord": "د ك ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "دُكَّتِ",
        "waznEnglish": "to crush, to level",
        "waznTlit": "dukkati",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "دَكَّةً",
        "answer": "(with) a crushing",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 478,
        "tlit": "dakkatan",
        "frequency": 7,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَحُمِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ وَالْجِبَالُ فَدُكَّتَا دَكَّةً وَاحِدَةً",
        "rootWord": "د ك ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "دَكَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "and crushed",
        "waznTlit": "dakkat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "دَانِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "hanging near",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "rootWordId": 488,
        "tlit": "dāniyatun",
        "frequency": 133,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 23,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " قُطُوفُهَا دَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "د ن و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "دَانِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "to draw",
        "waznTlit": "dāniyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِرَاعًا",
        "answer": "cubits",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 507,
        "tlit": "dhirāʿan",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 32,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ فِي سِلْسِلَةٍ ذَرْعُهَا سَبْعُونَ ذِرَاعًا فَاسْلُكُوهُ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ر ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذِرَاع",
        "waznEnglish": "his two forelegs",
        "waznTlit": "dhirāʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرْعُهَا",
        "answer": "its length",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 507,
        "tlit": "dharʿuhā",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 32,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ فِي سِلْسِلَةٍ ذَرْعُهَا سَبْعُونَ ذِرَاعًا فَاسْلُكُوهُ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ر ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذَرْع",
        "waznEnglish": "his two forelegs",
        "waznTlit": "dharʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "you take heed",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "rootWordId": 511,
        "tlit": "tadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": 292,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 42,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا بِقَوْلِ كَاهِنٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ك ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَذَكَّرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to receive admonition",
        "waznTlit": "tadhakkara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form V)",
        "waznFreq": 51,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْكِرَةً",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "rootWordId": 511,
        "tlit": "tadhkiratan",
        "frequency": 292,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " لِنَجْعَلَهَا لَكُمْ تَذْكِرَةً وَتَعِيَهَا أُذُنٌ وَاعِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ك ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَذْكِرَة",
        "waznEnglish": "Remember",
        "waznTlit": "tadhkirat",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 9,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَذْكِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a reminder",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "rootWordId": 511,
        "tlit": "latadhkiratun",
        "frequency": 292,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 48,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّهُ لَتَذْكِرَةٌ لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ك ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَذْكِرَة",
        "waznEnglish": "Remember",
        "waznTlit": "tadhkirat",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 9,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَى",
        "answer": "so you would see",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "fatarā",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 8,
        "arabicAyah": " فَتَرَى الْقَوْمَ فِيهَا صَرْعَىٰ كَأَنَّهُمْ أَعْجَازُ نَخْلٍ خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَهَلْ تَرَىٰ لَهُمْ مِنْ بَاقِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "892",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": 980,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَعَصَوْا رَسُولَ رَبِّهِمْ فَأَخَذَهُمْ أَخْذَةً رَابِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 975,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "893",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": 980,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْمَلَكُ عَلَىٰ أَرْجَائِهَا وَيَحْمِلُ عَرْشَ رَبِّكَ فَوْقَهُمْ يَوْمَئِذٍ ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 975,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "894",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": 980,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 43,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " تَنْزِيلٌ مِنْ رَبِّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 975,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "895",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": 980,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 52,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَبِّحْ بِاسْمِ رَبِّكَ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 975,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَابِيَةً",
        "answer": "exceeding",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "rootWordId": 529,
        "tlit": "rābiyatan",
        "frequency": 20,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " فَعَصَوْا رَسُولَ رَبِّهِمْ فَأَخَذَهُمْ أَخْذَةً رَابِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ر ب و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَّابِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and it swells",
        "waznTlit": "rābiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجَائِهَا",
        "answer": "its edges",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "rootWordId": 540,
        "tlit": "arjāihā",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْمَلَكُ عَلَىٰ أَرْجَائِهَا",
        "rootWord": "ر ج و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَرْجَآئ",
        "waznEnglish": "they hope",
        "waznTlit": "arjā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "461",
        "rootWordId": 555,
        "tlit": "rasūla",
        "frequency": 513,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَعَصَوْا رَسُولَ رَبِّهِمْ فَأَخَذَهُمْ أَخْذَةً رَابِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ر س ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَسُول",
        "waznEnglish": "[We] have sent you",
        "waznTlit": "rasūl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 332,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "462",
        "rootWordId": 555,
        "tlit": "rasūlin",
        "frequency": 513,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 40,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلُ رَسُولٍ كَرِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر س ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَسُول",
        "waznEnglish": "[We] have sent you",
        "waznTlit": "rasūl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 332,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاضِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "pleasant",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "rootWordId": 561,
        "tlit": "rāḍiyatin",
        "frequency": 73,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 21,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَهُوَ فِي عِيشَةٍ رَاضِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر ض و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَاضِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "will be pleased",
        "waznTlit": "rāḍiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرِيحٍ",
        "answer": "by a wind",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "rootWordId": 599,
        "tlit": "birīḥin",
        "frequency": 57,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا عَادٌ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِرِيحٍ صَرْصَرٍ عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر و ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رِيح",
        "waznEnglish": "you bring them in",
        "waznTlit": "rīḥ",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 29,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَبِّحْ",
        "answer": "So glorify",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "rootWordId": 651,
        "tlit": "fasabbiḥ",
        "frequency": 92,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 52,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَبِّحْ بِاسْمِ رَبِّكَ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "س ب ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَبَّحَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to glorify, to praise",
        "waznTlit": "sabbaḥa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 42,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعُونَ",
        "answer": "(is) seventy",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "rootWordId": 653,
        "tlit": "sabʿūna",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 32,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ فِي سِلْسِلَةٍ ذَرْعُهَا سَبْعُونَ ذِرَاعًا فَاسْلُكُوهُ",
        "rootWord": "س ب ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَبْع",
        "waznEnglish": "seven",
        "waznTlit": "sabʿ",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 23,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعَ",
        "answer": "(for) seven",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "rootWordId": 653,
        "tlit": "sabʿa",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " سَخَّرَهَا عَلَيْهِمْ سَبْعَ لَيَالٍ وَثَمَانِيَةَ أَيَّامٍ حُسُومًا",
        "rootWord": "س ب ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَبْع",
        "waznEnglish": "seven",
        "waznTlit": "sabʿ",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 23,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سَخَّرَهَا",
        "answer": "Which He imposed",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "rootWordId": 669,
        "tlit": "sakharahā",
        "frequency": 42,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " سَخَّرَهَا عَلَيْهِمْ سَبْعَ لَيَالٍ وَثَمَانِيَةَ أَيَّامٍ حُسُومًا",
        "rootWord": "س خ ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَخَّرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to subject, to impose",
        "waznTlit": "sakhara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 22,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the poor",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "rootWordId": 708,
        "tlit": "l-mis'kīni",
        "frequency": 69,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 34,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَحُضُّ عَلَىٰ طَعَامِ الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "rootWord": "س ك ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مِسْكِين",
        "waznEnglish": "Dwell",
        "waznTlit": "mis'kīn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 23,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سِلْسِلَةٍ",
        "answer": "a chain",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 712,
        "tlit": "sil'silatin",
        "frequency": 3,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 32,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ فِي سِلْسِلَةٍ ذَرْعُهَا سَبْعُونَ ذِرَاعًا فَاسْلُكُوهُ",
        "rootWord": "س ل س ل",
        "rootWordType": "quadriliteral root",
        "wazn": "س ل س ل",
        "waznEnglish": "and the chains",
        "waznTlit": "sīn lām sīn lām",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my authority",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "rootWordId": 713,
        "tlit": "sul'ṭāniyah",
        "frequency": 39,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 29,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " هَلَكَ عَنِّي سُلْطَانِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "س ل ط",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سُلْطَٰن",
        "waznEnglish": "surely He (would have) given them power",
        "waznTlit": "sul'ṭān",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 37,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْلَفْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you sent before you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "rootWordId": 714,
        "tlit": "aslaftum",
        "frequency": 8,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " كُلُوا وَاشْرَبُوا هَنِيئًا بِمَا أَسْلَفْتُمْ فِي الْأَيَّامِ الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "س ل ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَسْلَفَتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to do before, to send before",
        "waznTlit": "aslafat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْلُكُوهُ",
        "answer": "insert him",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "rootWordId": 716,
        "tlit": "fa-us'lukūhu",
        "frequency": 12,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 32,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ فِي سِلْسِلَةٍ ذَرْعُهَا سَبْعُونَ ذِرَاعًا فَاسْلُكُوهُ",
        "rootWord": "س ل ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "س ل ك",
        "waznEnglish": "to insert, to make enter",
        "waznTlit": "sīn lām kāf",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاسْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "bi-is'mi",
        "frequency": 381,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 52,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَبِّحْ بِاسْمِ رَبِّكَ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱسْم",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "is'm",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 39,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "l-samāu",
        "frequency": 381,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 16,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَانْشَقَّتِ السَّمَاءُ فَهِيَ يَوْمَئِذٍ وَاهِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "samā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 310,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "and drink",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 763,
        "tlit": "wa-ish'rabū",
        "frequency": 39,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " كُلُوا وَاشْرَبُوا هَنِيئًا بِمَا أَسْلَفْتُمْ فِي الْأَيَّامِ الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ش ر ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شَرِبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to drink",
        "waznTlit": "shariba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 15,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاعِرٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a poet",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "rootWordId": 778,
        "tlit": "shāʿirin",
        "frequency": 40,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 41,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِقَوْلِ شَاعِرٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ش ع ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شَاعِر",
        "waznEnglish": "they realize (it)",
        "waznTlit": "shāʿir",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْشَقَّتِ",
        "answer": "And will split",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "rootWordId": 787,
        "tlit": "wa-inshaqqati",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 16,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَانْشَقَّتِ السَّمَاءُ فَهِيَ يَوْمَئِذٍ وَاهِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ش ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱنشَقَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to split",
        "waznTlit": "inshaqqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form VII)",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِشِمَالِهِ",
        "answer": "in his left hand",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 798,
        "tlit": "bishimālihi",
        "frequency": 12,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِشِمَالِهِ فَيَقُولُ يَا لَيْتَنِي لَمْ أُوتَ كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ش م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شِّمَال",
        "waznEnglish": "contains",
        "waznTlit": "shimāl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 8,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرْصَرٍ",
        "answer": "screaming",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 835,
        "tlit": "ṣarṣarin",
        "frequency": 3,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا عَادٌ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِرِيحٍ صَرْصَرٍ عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ص ر ص ر",
        "rootWordType": "quadriliteral root",
        "wazn": "ص ر ص ر",
        "waznEnglish": "furious",
        "waznTlit": "ṣād rā ṣād rā",
        "waznType": "Adjective",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "fallen",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 837,
        "tlit": "ṣarʿā",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 11,
        "arabicAyah": " فَتَرَى الْقَوْمَ فِيهَا صَرْعَىٰ كَأَنَّهُمْ أَعْجَازُ نَخْلٍ خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ص ر ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ص ر ع",
        "waznEnglish": "fallen",
        "waznTlit": "ṣād rā ʿayn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلُّوهُ",
        "answer": "burn him",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "rootWordId": 858,
        "tlit": "ṣallūhu",
        "frequency": 25,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 31,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ الْجَحِيمَ صَلُّوهُ",
        "rootWord": "ص ل ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صَلُّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to burn",
        "waznTlit": "ṣallu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّورِ",
        "answer": "the trumpet ",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "rootWordId": 869,
        "tlit": "l-ṣūri",
        "frequency": 19,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَإِذَا نُفِخَ فِي الصُّورِ نَفْخَةٌ وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ص و ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صُّور",
        "waznEnglish": "and incline them",
        "waznTlit": "ṣūr",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 10,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامِ",
        "answer": "(the) feeding",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "rootWordId": 911,
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmi",
        "frequency": 48,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 34,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَحُضُّ عَلَىٰ طَعَامِ الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ط ع م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَعَام",
        "waznEnglish": "taste it",
        "waznTlit": "ṭaʿām",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 24,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامٌ",
        "answer": "any food",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "rootWordId": 911,
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmun",
        "frequency": 48,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 36,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا طَعَامٌ إِلَّا مِنْ غِسْلِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "ط ع م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَعَام",
        "waznEnglish": "taste it",
        "waznTlit": "ṭaʿām",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 24,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "طَغَى",
        "answer": "overflowed",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "rootWordId": 913,
        "tlit": "ṭaghā",
        "frequency": 39,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّا لَمَّا طَغَى الْمَاءُ حَمَلْنَاكُمْ فِي الْجَارِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ط غ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَغَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to transgress, to overflow",
        "waznTlit": "ṭaghā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالطَّاغِيَةِ",
        "answer": "by the overpowering (blast)",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "rootWordId": 913,
        "tlit": "bil-ṭāghiyati",
        "frequency": 39,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا ثَمُودُ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِالطَّاغِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ط غ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَّاغِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "transgress",
        "waznTlit": "ṭāghiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَنْتُ",
        "answer": "was certain",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "rootWordId": 944,
        "tlit": "ẓanantu",
        "frequency": 69,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 20,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنِّي ظَنَنْتُ أَنِّي مُلَاقٍ حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ظ ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ظَنَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to think, to assume, to guess",
        "waznTlit": "ẓanna",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 47,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "violent",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "rootWordId": 956,
        "tlit": "ʿātiyatin",
        "frequency": 10,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا عَادٌ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِرِيحٍ صَرْصَرٍ عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ت و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَاتِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and (were) insolent",
        "waznTlit": "ʿātiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْجَازُ",
        "answer": "trunks",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "rootWordId": 960,
        "tlit": "aʿjāzu",
        "frequency": 26,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 13,
        "arabicAyah": " فَتَرَى الْقَوْمَ فِيهَا صَرْعَىٰ كَأَنَّهُمْ أَعْجَازُ نَخْلٍ خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ج ز",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَعْجَاز",
        "waznEnglish": "Am I unable",
        "waznTlit": "aʿjāz",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرْشَ",
        "answer": "(the) Throne",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "rootWordId": 974,
        "tlit": "ʿarsha",
        "frequency": 33,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَحْمِلُ عَرْشَ رَبِّكَ فَوْقَهُمْ يَوْمَئِذٍ ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ع ر ش",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَرْش",
        "waznEnglish": "erect",
        "waznTlit": "ʿarsh",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 29,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تُعْرَضُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be exhibited",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 975,
        "tlit": "tuʿ'raḍūna",
        "frequency": 79,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 18,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ تُعْرَضُونَ لَا تَخْفَىٰ مِنْكُمْ خَافِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ع ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَرَضَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to display, to present, to expose, to turn away",
        "waznTlit": "ʿaraḍa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 11,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَصَوْا",
        "answer": "And they disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "rootWordId": 997,
        "tlit": "faʿaṣaw",
        "frequency": 32,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 10,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَعَصَوْا رَسُولَ رَبِّهِمْ فَأَخَذَهُمْ أَخْذَةً رَابِيَةً",
        "rootWord": "ع ص ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَصَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to disobey",
        "waznTlit": "ʿaṣā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 27,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "rootWordId": 1005,
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": 128,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 33,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ كَانَ لَا يُؤْمِنُ بِاللَّهِ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "ع ظ م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَظِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "honors",
        "waznTlit": "ʿaẓīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 120,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "rootWordId": 1005,
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": 128,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 52,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَبِّحْ بِاسْمِ رَبِّكَ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "ع ظ م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَظِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "honors",
        "waznTlit": "ʿaẓīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 120,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "surely know",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "lanaʿlamu",
        "frequency": 854,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 49,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّا لَنَعْلَمُ أَنَّ مِنْكُمْ مُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَلِمَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿalima",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 382,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "545",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": 854,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 43,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " تَنْزِيلٌ مِنْ رَبِّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَٰلَمِين",
        "waznEnglish": "they know",
        "waznTlit": "ʿālamīn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 73,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِيَةٍ",
        "answer": "elevated",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "rootWordId": 1018,
        "tlit": "ʿāliyatin",
        "frequency": 70,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 22,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فِي جَنَّةٍ عَالِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَالِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and Exalted",
        "waznTlit": "ʿāliyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَادٌ",
        "answer": "and Aad",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "rootWordId": 1035,
        "tlit": "waʿādun",
        "frequency": 63,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " كَذَّبَتْ ثَمُودُ وَعَادٌ بِالْقَارِعَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ع و د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَاد",
        "waznEnglish": "repeated",
        "waznTlit": "ʿād",
        "waznType": "Proper noun",
        "waznFreq": 24,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٌ",
        "answer": "Aad",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "rootWordId": 1035,
        "tlit": "ʿādun",
        "frequency": 63,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا عَادٌ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِرِيحٍ صَرْصَرٍ عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع و د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَاد",
        "waznEnglish": "repeated",
        "waznTlit": "ʿād",
        "waznType": "Proper noun",
        "waznFreq": 24,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "عِيشَةٍ",
        "answer": "a life",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1044,
        "tlit": "ʿīshatin",
        "frequency": 8,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 21,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَهُوَ فِي عِيشَةٍ رَاضِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ي ش",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عِيشَة",
        "waznEnglish": "a life",
        "waznTlit": "ʿīshat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "غِسْلِينٍ",
        "answer": "(the) discharge of wounds",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 1063,
        "tlit": "ghis'līnin",
        "frequency": 4,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 36,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا طَعَامٌ إِلَّا مِنْ غِسْلِينٍ",
        "rootWord": "غ س ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "غِسْلِين",
        "waznEnglish": "then wash",
        "waznTlit": "ghis'līn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَغُلُّوهُ",
        "answer": "and shackle him",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 1077,
        "tlit": "faghullūhu",
        "frequency": 16,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 30,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " خُذُوهُ فَغُلُّوهُ",
        "rootWord": "غ ل ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "غَلَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to defraud, to chain, to shackle",
        "waznTlit": "ghalla",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "has availed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "rootWordId": 1086,
        "tlit": "aghnā",
        "frequency": 73,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 28,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " مَا أَغْنَىٰ عَنِّي مَالِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "غ ن ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَغْنَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to avail, to prosper",
        "waznTlit": "aghnā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 15,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "rootWordId": 1164,
        "tlit": "fawqahum",
        "frequency": 43,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَحْمِلُ عَرْشَ رَبِّكَ فَوْقَهُمْ يَوْمَئِذٍ ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ف و ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "فَوْق",
        "waznEnglish": "he recovered",
        "waznTlit": "fawq",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Location adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 41,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَهُ",
        "answer": "before him",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "rootWordId": 1174,
        "tlit": "qablahu",
        "frequency": 294,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 9,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَجَاءَ فِرْعَوْنُ وَمَنْ قَبْلَهُ وَالْمُؤْتَفِكَاتُ بِالْخَاطِئَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ق ب ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَبْل",
        "waznEnglish": "will be accepted",
        "waznTlit": "qabl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 242,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْرَءُوا",
        "answer": "read",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "rootWordId": 1186,
        "tlit": "iq'raū",
        "frequency": 88,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 8,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ فَيَقُولُ هَاؤُمُ اقْرَءُوا كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ق ر أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَرَأَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to read, to recite",
        "waznTlit": "qara-a",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 16,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقَارِعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Striking Calamity",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 1193,
        "tlit": "bil-qāriʿati",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " كَذَّبَتْ ثَمُودُ وَعَادٌ بِالْقَارِعَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ق ر ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ق ر ع",
        "waznEnglish": "a disaster",
        "waznTlit": "qāf rā ʿayn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "rootWordId": 1201,
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": 33,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 38,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَا أُقْسِمُ بِمَا تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ق س م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَقْسَمُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to swear",
        "waznTlit": "aqsamu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 20,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَاضِيَةَ",
        "answer": "the end",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "rootWordId": 1212,
        "tlit": "l-qāḍiyata",
        "frequency": 63,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 27,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " يَا لَيْتَهَا كَانَتِ الْقَاضِيَةَ",
        "rootWord": "ق ض ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَاضِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "He decrees",
        "waznTlit": "qāḍiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَطَعْنَا",
        "answer": "certainly We (would) have cut off",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "rootWordId": 1215,
        "tlit": "laqaṭaʿnā",
        "frequency": 36,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 46,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ لَقَطَعْنَا مِنْهُ الْوَتِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ق ط ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قُطِعَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to cut",
        "waznTlit": "quṭiʿa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "قُطُوفُهَا",
        "answer": "Its clusters of fruits",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1216,
        "tlit": "quṭūfuhā",
        "frequency": 2,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 23,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " قُطُوفُهَا دَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ق ط ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ق ط ف",
        "waznEnglish": "Its clusters of fruits",
        "waznTlit": "qāf ṭā fā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "rootWordId": 1225,
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": 76,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 41,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِقَوْلِ شَاعِرٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ق ل ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَلِيل",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) little",
        "waznTlit": "qalīl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 70,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "rootWordId": 1225,
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": 76,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 42,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا بِقَوْلِ كَاهِنٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ق ل ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَلِيل",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) little",
        "waznTlit": "qalīl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 70,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "1576",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ فَيَقُولُ هَاؤُمُ اقْرَءُوا كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَالَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to say",
        "waznTlit": "qāla",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1618,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "1577",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِشِمَالِهِ فَيَقُولُ يَا لَيْتَنِي لَمْ أُوتَ كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَالَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to say",
        "waznTlit": "qāla",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1618,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "he (had) fabricated",
        "pcklId": "1619",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "taqawwala",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 44,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَوْ تَقَوَّلَ عَلَيْنَا بَعْضَ الْأَقَاوِيلِ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَقَوَّلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to fabricate, to make up",
        "waznTlit": "taqawwala",
        "waznType": "Verb (form V)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَقَاوِيلِ",
        "answer": "sayings",
        "pcklId": "1620",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "l-aqāwīli",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 44,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَوْ تَقَوَّلَ عَلَيْنَا بَعْضَ الْأَقَاوِيلِ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَقَاوِيل",
        "waznEnglish": "say",
        "waznTlit": "aqāwīl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "surely (the) Word",
        "pcklId": "1709",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "laqawlu",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 40,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلُ رَسُولٍ كَرِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَوْل",
        "waznEnglish": "say",
        "waznTlit": "qawl",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun",
        "waznFreq": 92,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "(is the) word",
        "pcklId": "1710",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "biqawli",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 41,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِقَوْلِ شَاعِرٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَوْل",
        "waznEnglish": "say",
        "waznTlit": "qawl",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun",
        "waznFreq": 92,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "(it is the) word",
        "pcklId": "1711",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "biqawli",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 42,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا بِقَوْلِ كَاهِنٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَوْل",
        "waznEnglish": "say",
        "waznTlit": "qawl",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun",
        "waznFreq": 92,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "483",
        "rootWordId": 1246,
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": 660,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 9,
        "arabicAyah": " فَتَرَى الْقَوْمَ فِيهَا صَرْعَىٰ كَأَنَّهُمْ أَعْجَازُ نَخْلٍ خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ق و م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَوْم",
        "waznEnglish": "they stand (still)",
        "waznTlit": "qawm",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 383,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "rootWordId": 1256,
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": 319,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ فَيَقُولُ هَاؤُمُ اقْرَءُوا كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ت ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِتَٰب",
        "waznEnglish": "write",
        "waznTlit": "kitāb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 260,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my record",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "rootWordId": 1256,
        "tlit": "kitābiyah",
        "frequency": 319,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 9,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ فَيَقُولُ هَاؤُمُ اقْرَءُوا كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ت ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِتَٰب",
        "waznEnglish": "write",
        "waznTlit": "kitāb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 260,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "rootWordId": 1256,
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": 319,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِشِمَالِهِ فَيَقُولُ يَا لَيْتَنِي لَمْ أُوتَ كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ت ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِتَٰب",
        "waznEnglish": "write",
        "waznTlit": "kitāb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 260,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my record",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "rootWordId": 1256,
        "tlit": "kitābiyah",
        "frequency": 319,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 25,
        "wordnum": 10,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِشِمَالِهِ فَيَقُولُ يَا لَيْتَنِي لَمْ أُوتَ كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ك ت ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِتَٰب",
        "waznEnglish": "write",
        "waznTlit": "kitāb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 260,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَتْ",
        "answer": "Denied",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "rootWordId": 1263,
        "tlit": "kadhabat",
        "frequency": 282,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " كَذَّبَتْ ثَمُودُ وَعَادٌ بِالْقَارِعَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ك ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَذَّبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to deny, to reject",
        "waznTlit": "kadhaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 176,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) deniers",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "rootWordId": 1263,
        "tlit": "mukadhibīna",
        "frequency": 282,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 49,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّا لَنَعْلَمُ أَنَّ مِنْكُمْ مُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ك ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُّكَذِّبِين",
        "waznEnglish": "[they] lie",
        "waznTlit": "mukadhibīn",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 21,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٍ",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "rootWordId": 1267,
        "tlit": "karīmin",
        "frequency": 47,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 40,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلُ رَسُولٍ كَرِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ك ر م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَرِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "You have honored",
        "waznTlit": "karīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 30,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "rootWordId": 1280,
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": 525,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 50,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّهُ لَحَسْرَةٌ عَلَى الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ك ف ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَٰفِرُون",
        "waznEnglish": "disbelieve[d]",
        "waznTlit": "kāfirūn",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 129,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاهِنٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a soothsayer",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 1300,
        "tlit": "kāhinin",
        "frequency": 2,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 42,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا بِقَوْلِ كَاهِنٍ قَلِيلًا مَا تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ك ه ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ك ه ن",
        "waznEnglish": "a soothsayer",
        "waznTlit": "kāf hā nūn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتِ",
        "answer": "had been",
        "pcklId": "1303",
        "rootWordId": 1305,
        "tlit": "kānati",
        "frequency": 1390,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 27,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " يَا لَيْتَهَا كَانَتِ الْقَاضِيَةَ",
        "rootWord": "ك و ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَانَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be",
        "waznTlit": "kāna",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1358,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1304",
        "rootWordId": 1305,
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": 1390,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 33,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ كَانَ لَا يُؤْمِنُ بِاللَّهِ الْعَظِيمِ",
        "rootWord": "ك و ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَانَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be",
        "waznTlit": "kāna",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1358,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلَاقٍ",
        "answer": "(will) meet",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "rootWordId": 1347,
        "tlit": "mulāqin",
        "frequency": 146,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 20,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنِّي ظَنَنْتُ أَنِّي مُلَاقٍ حِسَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ل ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُلَٰق",
        "waznEnglish": "they meet",
        "waznTlit": "mulāq",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form III)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "So not",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "rootWordId": 1363,
        "tlit": "falaysa",
        "frequency": 89,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 35,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَيْسَ لَهُ الْيَوْمَ هَاهُنَا حَمِيمٌ",
        "rootWord": "ل ي س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ل ي س",
        "waznEnglish": "to not be",
        "waznTlit": "lām yā sīn",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 89,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَالٍ",
        "answer": "nights",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "rootWordId": 1364,
        "tlit": "layālin",
        "frequency": 92,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " سَخَّرَهَا عَلَيْهِمْ سَبْعَ لَيَالٍ وَثَمَانِيَةَ أَيَّامٍ حُسُومًا",
        "rootWord": "ل ي ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "لَيْل",
        "waznEnglish": "of the night",
        "waznTlit": "layl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 84,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَلَكُ",
        "answer": "And the Angels",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "rootWordId": 1415,
        "tlit": "wal-malaku",
        "frequency": 206,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 17,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْمَلَكُ عَلَىٰ أَرْجَائِهَا وَيَحْمِلُ عَرْشَ رَبِّكَ فَوْقَهُمْ يَوْمَئِذٍ ثَمَانِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "م ل ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَلَك",
        "waznEnglish": "possesses",
        "waznTlit": "malak",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 88,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالِيَهْ",
        "answer": "my wealth",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "rootWordId": 1427,
        "tlit": "māliyah",
        "frequency": 86,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 28,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " مَا أَغْنَىٰ عَنِّي مَالِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "م و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "م و ل",
        "waznEnglish": "[the] wealth",
        "waznTlit": "mīm wāw lām",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 86,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the water",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "rootWordId": 1428,
        "tlit": "l-māu",
        "frequency": 63,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 11,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّا لَمَّا طَغَى الْمَاءُ حَمَلْنَاكُمْ فِي الْجَارِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "م و ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "م و ه",
        "waznEnglish": "water",
        "waznTlit": "mīm wāw hā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 63,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخْلٍ",
        "answer": "(of) date-palms",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "rootWordId": 1452,
        "tlit": "nakhlin",
        "frequency": 20,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 14,
        "arabicAyah": " فَتَرَى الْقَوْمَ فِيهَا صَرْعَىٰ كَأَنَّهُمْ أَعْجَازُ نَخْلٍ خَاوِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ن خ ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَخْل",
        "waznEnglish": "the date-palm",
        "waznTlit": "nakhl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 11,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلٌ",
        "answer": "(It is) a revelation",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "rootWordId": 1460,
        "tlit": "tanzīlun",
        "frequency": 293,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 43,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " تَنْزِيلٌ مِنْ رَبِّ الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "rootWord": "ن ز ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَنزِيل",
        "waznEnglish": "it descended",
        "waznTlit": "tanzīl",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 15,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفِخَ",
        "answer": "is blown",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "rootWordId": 1496,
        "tlit": "nufikha",
        "frequency": 20,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَإِذَا نُفِخَ فِي الصُّورِ نَفْخَةٌ وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ن ف خ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَفَخَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to blow, to breathe",
        "waznTlit": "nafakha",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 19,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْخَةٌ",
        "answer": "a blast",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "rootWordId": 1496,
        "tlit": "nafkhatun",
        "frequency": 20,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَإِذَا نُفِخَ فِي الصُّورِ نَفْخَةٌ وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "ن ف خ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَفْخَة",
        "waznEnglish": "then I breath",
        "waznTlit": "nafkhat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "هَلَكَ",
        "answer": "Is gone",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 1559,
        "tlit": "halaka",
        "frequency": 68,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 29,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " هَلَكَ عَنِّي سُلْطَانِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ه ل ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "هَلَكَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to die, to be destroyed",
        "waznTlit": "halaka",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 5,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُهْلِكُوا",
        "answer": "they were destroyed",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "rootWordId": 1559,
        "tlit": "fa-uh'likū",
        "frequency": 68,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا ثَمُودُ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِالطَّاغِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ه ل ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَهْلَكَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to destroy",
        "waznTlit": "ahlaka",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 51,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأُهْلِكُوا",
        "answer": "they were destroyed",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "rootWordId": 1559,
        "tlit": "fa-uh'likū",
        "frequency": 68,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا عَادٌ فَأُهْلِكُوا بِرِيحٍ صَرْصَرٍ عَاتِيَةٍ",
        "rootWord": "ه ل ك",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَهْلَكَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to destroy",
        "waznTlit": "ahlaka",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 51,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "هَنِيئًا",
        "answer": "(in) satisfaction",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 1567,
        "tlit": "hanīan",
        "frequency": 4,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " كُلُوا وَاشْرَبُوا هَنِيئًا بِمَا أَسْلَفْتُمْ فِي الْأَيَّامِ الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ه ن أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ه ن أ",
        "waznEnglish": "(in) satisfaction",
        "waznTlit": "hā nūn hamza",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَتِينَ",
        "answer": "the aorta",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1584,
        "tlit": "l-watīna",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 46,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " ثُمَّ لَقَطَعْنَا مِنْهُ الْوَتِينَ",
        "rootWord": "و ت ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "و ت ن",
        "waznEnglish": "the aorta",
        "waznTlit": "wāw tā nūn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "rootWordId": 1593,
        "tlit": "wāḥidatun",
        "frequency": 68,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 13,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " فَإِذَا نُفِخَ فِي الصُّورِ نَفْخَةٌ وَاحِدَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "و ح د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَٰحِدَة",
        "waznEnglish": "(of) one (kind)",
        "waznTlit": "wāḥidat",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 31,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "rootWordId": 1593,
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": 68,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 14,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " وَحُمِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ وَالْجِبَالُ فَدُكَّتَا دَكَّةً وَاحِدَةً",
        "rootWord": "و ح د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَٰحِدَة",
        "waznEnglish": "(of) one (kind)",
        "waznTlit": "wāḥidat",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)",
        "waznFreq": 31,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعِيَهَا",
        "answer": "and would be conscious of it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1628,
        "tlit": "wataʿiyahā",
        "frequency": 7,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " لِنَجْعَلَهَا لَكُمْ تَذْكِرَةً وَتَعِيَهَا أُذُنٌ وَاعِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "و ع ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَعِيَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be conscious",
        "waznTlit": "taʿiya",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاعِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "conscious",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "rootWordId": 1628,
        "tlit": "wāʿiyatun",
        "frequency": 7,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 12,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " لِنَجْعَلَهَا لَكُمْ تَذْكِرَةً وَتَعِيَهَا أُذُنٌ وَاعِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "و ع ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَٰعِيَة",
        "waznEnglish": "and would be conscious of it",
        "waznTlit": "wāʿiyat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَعَتِ",
        "answer": "will occur",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "rootWordId": 1639,
        "tlit": "waqaʿati",
        "frequency": 24,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 15,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَيَوْمَئِذٍ وَقَعَتِ الْوَاقِعَةُ",
        "rootWord": "و ق ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَقَعَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to fall, to occur, to fulfill",
        "waznTlit": "waqaʿa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَاقِعَةُ",
        "answer": "the Occurrence",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "rootWordId": 1639,
        "tlit": "l-wāqiʿatu",
        "frequency": 24,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 15,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَيَوْمَئِذٍ وَقَعَتِ الْوَاقِعَةُ",
        "rootWord": "و ق ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَاقِعَة",
        "waznEnglish": "(became) incumbent",
        "waznTlit": "wāqiʿat",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "for the Allah-fearing",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "rootWordId": 1641,
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": 258,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 48,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّهُ لَتَذْكِرَةٌ لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "rootWord": "و ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُتَّقِين",
        "waznEnglish": "and save us",
        "waznTlit": "muttaqīn",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form VIII)",
        "waznFreq": 49,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاهِيَةٌ",
        "answer": "frail",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1653,
        "tlit": "wāhiyatun",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 16,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَانْشَقَّتِ السَّمَاءُ فَهِيَ يَوْمَئِذٍ وَاهِيَةٌ",
        "rootWord": "و ه ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "و ه ي",
        "waznEnglish": "frail",
        "waznTlit": "wāw hā yā",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَقِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) certainty",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "rootWordId": 1660,
        "tlit": "l-yaqīni",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 51,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِنَّهُ لَحَقُّ الْيَقِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ي ق ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَقِين",
        "waznEnglish": "firmly believe",
        "waznTlit": "yaqīn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 8,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "answer": "in his right hand",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "rootWordId": 1662,
        "tlit": "biyamīnihi",
        "frequency": 71,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 19,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ فَيَقُولُ هَاؤُمُ اقْرَءُوا كِتَابِيَهْ",
        "rootWord": "ي م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَمِين",
        "waznEnglish": "the right",
        "waznTlit": "yamīn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 65,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "by the right hand",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "rootWordId": 1662,
        "tlit": "bil-yamīni",
        "frequency": 71,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 45,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " لَأَخَذْنَا مِنْهُ بِالْيَمِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ي م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَمِين",
        "waznEnglish": "the right",
        "waznTlit": "yamīn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 65,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "days",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "rootWordId": 1664,
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": 405,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " سَخَّرَهَا عَلَيْهِمْ سَبْعَ لَيَالٍ وَثَمَانِيَةَ أَيَّامٍ حُسُومًا",
        "rootWord": "ي و م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ي و م",
        "waznEnglish": "(of the) Day",
        "waznTlit": "yā wāw mīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 405,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَيَّامِ",
        "answer": "the days",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "rootWordId": 1664,
        "tlit": "l-ayāmi",
        "frequency": 405,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 24,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " كُلُوا وَاشْرَبُوا هَنِيئًا بِمَا أَسْلَفْتُمْ فِي الْأَيَّامِ الْخَالِيَةِ",
        "rootWord": "ي و م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ي و م",
        "waznEnglish": "(of the) Day",
        "waznTlit": "yā wāw mīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 405,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "rootWordId": 1664,
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": 405,
        "surahnum": 69,
        "ayahnum": 35,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَيْسَ لَهُ الْيَوْمَ هَاهُنَا حَمِيمٌ",
        "rootWord": "ي و م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ي و م",
        "waznEnglish": "(of the) Day",
        "waznTlit": "yā wāw mīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 405,
        "hasRootWord": true
    }
]; 
export default words;